<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastian Vega Uribe</title>
    <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sebastian Vega Uribe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Data Analysis: A Comprehensive Guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Data Types: We&amp;rsquo;ll begin by introducing readers to the different types of data encountered in data analysis, such as numerical, categorical, and ordinal data. We&amp;rsquo;ll explain the characteristics and significance of each data type, and provide examples to help readers better understand how to identify and work with different data types in their analyses.
Data Collection Methods: In this section, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore various data collection methods, such as surveys, interviews, and observational studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Data Analysis: A Comprehensive Guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
